export default [
    {
      question: "What is TheOdd1sOut's real name?",
      choice1: "James",
      choice2: "Steve",
      choice3: "Adam",
      choice4: "Pete",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "What is TheOdd1sOut's surname?",
      choice1: "Carter",
      choice2: "Frank",
      choice3: "Rallison",
      choice4: "Smith",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "How many books has TheOdd1sOut written/illustrated? (as of May 2023)",
      choice1: "10",
      choice2: "4",
      choice3: "2",
      choice4: "5",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "When did TheOdd1sOut create his YouTube channel?",
      choice1: "5th May 2014",
      choice2: "14th August 2016",
      choice3: "27th Feburary 2013",
      choice4: "30th August 2014",
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "What is TheOdd1sOut show called?",
      choice1: "Pickles",
      choice2: "OddBalls",
      choice3: "TheOddShow",
      choice4: "OddBods",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "Which school did TheOdd1sOut go to?",
      choice1: "Perry High School",
      choice2: "Morganville High School",
      choice3: "Adamsfield High School",
      choice4: "Chandler High School",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many siblings does TheOdd1sOut have?",
      choice1: "None",
      choice2: "2",
      choice3: "4",
      choice4: "3",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Where was TheOdd1sOut born?",
      choice1: "Gilbert, Arizona, USA",
      choice2: "Chandler, Arizona, USA",
      choice3: "Silicon Valley, California, USA",
      choice4: "Las Vegas, Nevada, USA",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
      question: "TheOdd1sOut is ____ handed?",
      choice1: "Left",
      choice2: "Right",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "How many songs has TheOdd1sOut made?",
      choice1: "1",
      choice2: "3",
      choice3: "5",
      choice4: "2",
      answer: 4,
    },
    {
      question: "Who did TheOdd1sOut collaborate with to make the song 'Life is Fun'?", 
      choice1: "RoomieOfficial",
      choice2: "TwoSetViolin",
      choice3: "Boyinaband",
      choice4: "Dream",
      answer: 3,
    },
    {
      question: "Where did TheOdd1sOut use to work?",
      choice1: "Subway",
      choice2: "McDonalds",
      choice3: "Wendys",
      choice4: "Taco Bell",
      answer: 1,
    },
    {
      question: "Which year was TheOdd1sOut born?",
      choice1: "1993",
      choice2: "1996",
      choice3: "1985",
      choice4: "2005",
      answer: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "What is TheOdd1sOut's favourite colour?",
        choice1: "Blue",
        choice2: "Green",
        choice3: "Red",
        choice4: "Magenta",
        answer: 4,
    },
    {
        question: "What is TheOdd1sOut's birthday?",
        choice1: "2nd May",
        choice2: "14th August",
        choice3: "14th May",
        choice4: "27th Feburary",
        answer: 3,
    },
  ];
  